ISLAND OF SAN MAN
We drink later, we must guard
tonight.
Listen to me, working properly.
If you work well, I'll treat you drink
.
He was good as well.
Let's start the meeting.
[ALL]
General Life!
Regarding this issue...
Where Chul-Bong?
- You're all useless.
- It was all my fault-General.
What are you saying?
I want you to be weak.
Who is the person who contributed it?
Cham-bok you who contributed.
I see you save our ship.
Jang Sa-jung come here.
Actually I did not do anything.
Do you have the expertise,
I will lift you into Vicegerent.
- I do not want.
- You have no other choice.
- Really?
- I'm giving you a great opportunity.
- I can not do anything.
- I want you to represent me catch pirates.
What? You're a sly one, are you afraid of them
so you send me to hell.
Watch your mouth, you know you're talking to
?
I'm young, I'm not married and still a virgin
.
Do you want revenge on my father?
You know the notorious pirates,
you take advantage of it.
Shut up, how dare you defy me!
When I was just lucky, but you misunderstand
.
- I quit the military.
- Kill him!
- Do not.
- He's been presumptuous.
He is still very young.
Do not be hasty.
Captain.
Hold.
I swear you must die.
Everything, Jang Sa-jung fight outside.
Come on out.
Basic traitor kill him!
Do not let life, kill everything!
Keep the ship.
Catch him!
Arrest that woman!
We won, you see aksiku
?
So who among you are the captain of this ship?
- Are you the one?
- Not me.
I do not know.
Yeo-wool because you've been deserving
you who decide their fate.
You represent me,
follow his orders.
[ALL] Ready!
See what we found.
I guess they all are prisoners here.
Do not be afraid, you're all safe.
Miss.
- Do not be impertinent.
- Help me, I'm looking for my son.
- Why did you get caught?
- I'm looking for a job.
They said I was only going to be a servant.
Vice captain, what should we do on their
?
- You're here.
- Stempelnya fall.
What is this?
This is all your fault, why are you careless
?
I do not accidentally.
If we lose the stamp
what will happen to us?
Did he survive?
3 DAYS LATER
We get a big booty
we must celebrate.
Let's toast to our cooperation.
As promised, I will help you seize the throne
and I got most of this country.
As a fellow man we have big ambitions.
Now look I've got five royal seal
.
I collect a lot of money after the first
I will retire.
Seldom has an animal on board,
where did you get that dog?
This dog I got from the merchant vessel,
he just come with me.
We just think of him as booty.
- You're kidding right?
- We should be proud as a great pirate.
But why did you reject my love?
- Do not know shame.
I was so convinced
someday you will fall into my arms.
- Not possible.
- Why not possible?
- You've got a wife.
- True, but a real man
obliged to spread love everywhere.
Idiot, you're drunk, you talk nonsense
and mouth odor.
Do you already have children.
I am very responsible.
If the lady does not take the stamp of the sea,
I'd be dead.
No way, I believe the captain
not that cruel.
You're so great, you just jump into the sea
.
Compared with you, what can you do huh
?
- What do we do stamp it?
- Perhaps we sell.
Captain  Why not tell us?
Basic old drunks.
Basic useless, if not enemies
wine that will kill you.
Ouch, my head dizzy.
I just took mine, the bastard
usurp the throne from me.
Seize the stamp is an easy affair
but attacking another story palace.
Who is he?
Is she the palace?
- You'd better collect a lot of troops.
- I have to go.
- Mo Hong-gab.
- Yes.
- Choon-Sub
- Yong-hood.
- Yes.
- Han Sang-vol.
- Yes. I'm here.
-
Iiege - Yes.
- He Ma.
- I'm here.
I have to fast, I had no food supplies
.
Damn, once the cold night wind.
Get them.
- Ready!
- Get them.
Captain, why they were arrested?
They are not incompetent, almost
booty we lost.
I'm sorry. Captain.
- They have long struggled with us.
- We are pirates.
- This is our rule.
- Captain.
- Captain, your men were fair?
- You're not allowed to get my daughter.
But you should have a girl in tow.
- Take him.
- Do not, let go of me.
Do not touch me, do not!
Shut up.
- You are so cruel.
- I am your captain.
- Let go of me!
- The lives you are mine.
You all....
Kill him.
Captain, your men rebelled.
You remind me of myself.
You're not my father.
I know you deserve punishment.
You said it, we follow the rules
pirates pirates.
How can you survive without me?
I'm proud of you.
Get rid of that flag.
Majesty, the pirates attacked our ship
. We lost five stamps.
I want you to investigate this matter and find out
who stole it.
Royal seal is a symbol of power
lose it very embarrassing.
I made you General,
pursue and destroy the pirates.
Live His Majesty!
- Finally I became General also.
- It should be celebrated.
- But I'm still confused.
- About what?
Where we have to look for the pirates?
The oceans are very large, we do not even have a clue
.
How can we find them?
Leave it to me.
- What is it?
- There is something approaching.
I want all the soldiers getting in
positions respectively.
Prepare for war!
Ready!
Shoot arrows!
- It was gray whales.
- It's our lucky day.
- Kill the whales!
- Damn. Shoot the cannon!
- Shoot the cannon!
Shoot the cannon!
That's it, do not let him get away!
Artillerymen, shoot!
- Shoot!
- My ship.
- Captain.
Stempelku.
Stempelku, he swallowed it.
Where are you guys?
I want to eat!
Come I will not hurt you.
Where are you guys?
Let me eat you.
I'm so hungry.
It's been a long time I did not eat.
Help me.
We caught him in the woods.
So tell me, who are you?
I am member of the pirate Black Crow
brave,
If you do not let go of me,
my friends will find me.
I can not guarantee your safety
so for your own sake, be wise.
Gosh, you're good at boasting.
- You look like a fool.
- What?
My friend said I was cute.
The woman also likes me.
I do not lie.
- I believe.
- Do you believe?
- It's you cerdasjuga.
- I believe you're stupid.
- I guess it's not funny.
- Hey you.
Why are you here?
A very long story.
Actually captain conspired with someone and he wants to kill us all.
I accidentally heard it
so I went on the boat before I was killed.
I'm sure he's a palace,
because he wanted to seize the throne.
If I see him again I will kill him.
Enough .
Your story is true or not, does not become a problem
.
You will become a servant at the camp.
I refused, I am the person dignity,
I do not want to be a slave.
- Quick work funny guy.
- Why do not you first looked in the mirror?
What did you say?
There is an important issue.
Majesty seems angry.
What? You all can not get it!
What have you done!
Ampun! Mercy.
What do you think?
Actually there is nothing I can think again,
I do not want to get involved in this issue.
What do you mean?
Do not like it,
no need to get upset like that to me.
I'll help you.
But I'm in danger.
Anything else? There is nothing you can do anymore.
Do not you remember yesterday's events?
You're not going to be involved.
Do you remember back.
What has been done by him?
- Ampun! Forgive me, Your Majesty!
- What is it? Why do you ask for forgiveness?
I've been guilty of letting him get away from my hand.
I've caught him and held him.
But I was not able to run the task.
What?
- Majesty.
- You're it.
You're not useless at all!
Forgive me, Your Majesty.
But I brought this for you.
What is this? What are you taking me?
This is an insult!
- You know what I mean by all this?
- I'm sorry, Your Honor.
- Why be like this?
- Forgive me, Your Majesty!
I also ask for forgiveness, Your Honor.
I please do not punish him.
You do not need to interfere!
You also will I cut off!
I do not want to know, you must
catch back dead or alive.
- Well, Your Honor. But...
- Do it!
Do it as soon as possible.
- You all understand?
- Yes, Your Honor.
I know I'll be able to get away with
easily from there. Just with anything.
- Magna.
- Yes.
You have prepared a net for them.
We will catch them.
Chairman, is not it better
aja we attack directly.
- You do not say anything, you do not understand anything.
- Why is it always like that?
They are coming.
- Cut now. Yes, cut.
- Cut now? Cut?
- Cut now. True. Do it.
- Now also?
- What an idiot. Come retreat.
- Backward. Backward.
What's up?
Come all! Attack!
Let's attack!
Tankap them!
Catch!
Alas! Let's spread!
Let's all spread out!
Chairman!
- Arrows over there!
- Over there!
Do not leave me, chief!
- Do not leave me, chief!
- Capture!
Go there.
Come on, come on!
Do not run!
- You run over there!
- Wait for me, chief!
Exhausting all.
- That was a stupid act.
- I also do not understand his command.
I told you not to cut it.
But you do it anyway.
Why be like this?
So all because of him.
All failed because of an error he.
Why do you keep blaming everyone else?
You are planning all this.
But you blame the other person.
Just kidding.
You do not need to upset anyone else.
And they could not chase us.
We've escaped.
Chairman, Chairman.
Look, look, over there.
- They're still chasing us.
- True sekai. What now?
What now?
What should we do now?
Chairman.
I in live again.
What this really him?
You're lucky.
- I have an important task for you.
- What can I do?
You have to kill someone.
If you can do it, I will membebaskamu.
It was an attractive offer.
- That's why I say you're lucky.
- Very true, very lucky.
You'd better enjoy this dish first, new
you do your job.
I wanted to do it.
- What now?
- I'm sure he succeeded.
You do not have to worry.
- What did you come here?
- I want to say something.
What is it? You say it directly.
No need to wait anymore.
I want to convey a
information that may be useful to armadamu.
You're so lucky.
If that information is quite useful for
aramdaku, I would be very grateful.
There will be ships that will attack you.
Ship what? Ships which can beat the greatness of my ship's
? That is very great.
- You're not messing with me, right?
- Bastard.
- You are too arrogant.
- It is true, what if I'm arrogant?
You know, you're no match for me.
You will never defeat me.
- We can not let this happen. Come in action.
- You do not like it.
- You do not need to interfere.
- He was abs.
We have to be patient first.
When it was time we will attack.
- When is the right time?
- Immediately.
Let's go.
I really like in here, there is so much food
.
- What creature is that?
- Come on, do not be in view.
- I'm sure the creature is not from here.
- Come on we have to keep moving.
And I do it like this.
I like it vibrates.
Do you like my story?
Are you impressed with kehebatanku?
- What is it? If you do what I can.
- No need to worry. We're not trying to kill you.
Do you want something?
Information.
- You'd better say it.
- I do not know anything.
You should remove me.
- If you do not let me go, feel the consequences.
- It's just talk.
Ampun! Well, I would say.
But this information is not free.
- I want something in return.
- What is it? Katakanllah.
You let go of me first.
I will soon tell you.
- He wants to trick us.
- I promise.
What?
What's up? No longer met.
What brought you here?
I'm fine.
And what is that.
Why do you still like it?
Do not you miss me?
Relax. No need to like it.
We have not met.
I'm do not want to mess around.
I'm here to do something.
Why do you still like it?
Not at all alert.
How?
Do you still do the little things?
Looks like the night would be long.
All here. I hope you can help.
Tell me what you know information?
Of course, there is an information for all of these.
Only, it seems this is not enough.
- Really?
- This is a very valuable information.
And also there are others who would like information
I got this. You may have to pay more.
How much do you want?
What all this is not enough?
Say. Or you not be able to go from here
.
- Okay.
- Good.
Shit, he caught it.
Slow down, we will get it back.
No need to worry.
- What do you mean?
- Listen, you first patient.
I want to tell you something.
And this story a long time before the kingdom.
- It may already be a legend now.
- You're just bragging!
- What?
- I just wanted to come here.
And this seems to have matured.
It's time to enjoy it.
Okay, everything is ready.
Actually no I want to say to you
all, I hope you are not surprised by it.
- Well, you say it.
- What would you say?
- What is important? - Of course, very important.
- Come on, just say it already.
- Do you want to hear?
- You listen wrote him first.
- Come on, the better we all sit down.
- Come on, just say it.
- Never mind tomorrow.
- I'm sorry, I'm sleepy.
What you would all that much gold?
All right, listen up. Come listen.
- What do you mean?
- What are you talking about?
- Come on, you say.
- Are not you sleepy?
- You say it, or I'll get out of here!
- Okay.
- How do you say?
- Damn, what do you mean?
- Let's say, come quickly.
- Maybe we should put it off until tomorrow.
What do you mean? Do you want to fight me?
Are you dare to fight me? You're great?
Forgive me.
I'm sorry, I have to hit him.
Come on, you say that now.
Right.
But you put it first.
What is not there is honor?
What you all have dared to fight me?
- What you want to do exactly?
- What?
- Like it alone.
- True. It was easy as pie.
But we do not have enough strength.
- That's why I like you.
- What do you mean?
We can do it, if we want to.
You're great to talk,
, you see, we are short of people.
- Are you kidding?
- He was funny once.
- Calm down, calm down.
- Calm?
Okay, here we go.
Who wants to join?
- You do not always want to hit people.
- Never mind.
He was always like that.
Always show sinister faces.
Do you hear, there is nothing to fear.
I always follow your words,
like that time I always take care of you.
- It should you like it.
- Who told talk? And I did all that.
- Great all.
- Of course.
- Always nonsense. I've had it with you.
- You do not need to do that! Come on!
Do you challenge me? Come on!
Come on, do not you run.
Actually I want to say,
I love you all like brothers.
I'm willing to sacrifice this for my brothers.
Whatever will I do for my brother.
Although should do it all.
All the things I would do. Everything.
All will I face for my brother.
Everything.
And you do not realize it.
All sacrifice.
- What are you doing?
- You've finished? What I have to end?
End?
Never mind do not mess around.
Tomorrow, we will act.
This is very useful in long-range combat.
And over there.
A very great thing once.
It can kill in an instant.
And right here. A new object.
It was great once.
Can
kill many enemies with a single attack from afar.
Do you already know what you want?
This is very dangerous. Over here.
There are other things I want to show you.
Note.
See the fine.
Enemies will not get away from this.
We recommend that you back off a little.
You take it easy, I'm not okay.
What are you doing?
You hit the arrow...
What is it?
Blast what is it?
He's the one.
It is very difficult.
How can you survive?
Arrow is not painful.
Give me a break.
Hey, are you ready?
Yes.
Come on, here we go!
Come on!
Prepare everything.
We will sail soon.
Prepare our weapons.
Tell them to keep pace.
We will soon be up.
Hoist screen.
I'm so tired.
Finally we arrived.
This is not the end of our adventure.
This is just the beginning of our adventure.
You're all still excited.
We're going to win.
Show me all your passion!
With all our strength.
Come sail!
Come on!
- What?
- What would you like to ask again?
You should pay attention to.
It hurts.
Majesty...
They made it to shore
Majesty not to worry.
Soldiers we have been pursuing them.
This problem will soon be completed.
Do not worry.
We have sent the best soldiers
they will not fail.
We will promptly notify you.
Good. Immediately
finish this task.
And make sure they are all dead.
Do not forgive them.
Do you understand?
Sucks.
He can only commands us alone.
Do not complain too much.
Right.
What do you think?
Do you even think about it?
Because of this, our plan was all messed up.
Do you have other plans?
Tell me if you've got...
Can not you shut up for a moment?
You are disturbing my concentration.
Are you tired of living?
Not...
But those guys got away...
I excused myself.
These workers worked very diligently.
I'm sure this will be completed soon.
Soon... soon finish this.
Take it easy. It will be completed
as you wish.
I can not wait.
I can not wait to see the results of your work.
Right. I understand.
Soon I could sail.
Hey! Hey!
You can not drink the water.
I'm thirsty.
- Sharks!
- Sharks.
- There are sharks!
- What should we do?
The shark will come here.
We have to fight.
- Kill the shark!
- Be prepared!
He came! Oh, No!
It's falling!
Hold on!
Sharks are coming!
Do something!
Hold this rope!
Hold on!
We made it!
We kill the shark!
We survived!
Like I expected.
Yes, sir. This ship is very strong.
Now, we just need to find the target.
This ship will be the fastest ship...
What's that noise?
I do not hear anything.
Ship what is it?
It was weird.
Hold on! Hang in there!
Kill her!
Kill!
The bullet fell!
Let's turn it on!
We will die !
- Fast! Fast!
- Can not turn on.
It lights up!
- Attack them.
- Attack them!
- We're going to die.
- Do not say that.
- Shoot them!
Who are they?
What did he want them?
I do not understand.
Who? They?
Finally, it's over.
Help me pull the rope.
I'm not sure about this.
He is still alive!
- What is it?
- The shark is dead.
- We managed to kill the shark!
- We managed to kill him!
We're great!
It's just a fish.
What should we do with this shark?
Is it edible?
I never eat it, is not that nice?
We do not even know how to cook it.
Maybe we could just burn it.
What did you say?
No need to worry about.
Meat
for this may be enough for us all to eat.
Maybe we can leave for the needs.
What happened?
Why could explode?
We're ready to shoot.
We're about her!
Shot sangatjitu.
Guarding her very strict.
If we get caught, we're going to be put to death.
I hear they are very cruel.
Hey, listen. I have a plan.
Say it.
We can divert their attention.
Who will distract them?
We can pretend to be dead.
They will not care about the dead.
There might be another way.
Think about it.
We can not wait anymore.
You'll do it.
True at all...
Are you sure  with a plan like this?
I need some people.
Please.
Him. Him.
Do not pretend sad when I see you.
You are making me like this.
Do not fight.
Right.
After I distract them,
you should immediately go.
And then I'll
hiding somewhere.
And swim like...
You should, too.
Can you do it?
With so they will not notice it.
Then we'll sneak.
Then one person would go and sneak.
Then steal the treasure.
While others watched from outside
to keep you.
If it's safe,
we will give you a sign.
But you should not be up ketauan.
Defeat  some guards.
Do not forget to ask for forgiveness.
After that we definitely made it into the main room.
In a food storage warehouse.
Then we sprinkle oil all over the place
then fled from there.
- Okay.
- You always say that & apos; & apos; Well & apos; & apos ;.
Give me a little advice.
Do not always accept the suggestions,
You is its chairman.
You are supposed to do this.
My lord, it's safe.
Fixed Heightened security.
Do not let anyone escape.
Harden guard!
What is this?
Why do they patrol?
What is it?
See it!
Are they aware of our existence?
It is not possible.
Has he been caught?
My lord, look at that!
It!
No way!
He came!
Prepare everything. He came.
Immediately hoist screen!
Quick!
Quick. Quick.
Who are you?
Fast, fast, fast, fast.
Get out of here!
Chairman!
Less sharp knife.
Quick jump!
Death to you all!
Kill him!
Turns out you!
Why are you messing my kingdom?
Hurry up!
I do not know it's you here.
You dare to mess up my place.
Do you forget who you are?
Death to you!
Look at you, you're even still weak.
I'm not going to lose again.
Come on.
Quick! Hurry!
Hurry!
- Hyeon Chung!
- Catch it!
Pull! Pull!
Yikes!
Let's go!
We will meet again!
What is news?
We missed the boat again.
It could not be anymore.
This is a very clever pirate.
He came from the darkness of night.
And attacked my ship.
I do not care, we should be able to secure the region
, but should only patrol boat.
We are short of troops.
We can not give a lot of patrol boats.
Do you understand the situation?
But if this continues, we will ship damaged
continue.
Do you want to sacrifice our ship?
We'll see.
Secure all of this!
We know this village plotting with
pirates.
Mother!
Come on, go!
Come on!
See this.
This is not good,
All we would swim.
Find and grab as much as possible.
Let's do it.
There is a whale!
It's right there!
Quick look.
- Wow.
- Great once.
- It was huge!
- Yes!
Do not miss!
Captain? What can?
Not. What is it?
Not. Stop.
That she is the parent.
What?
Yes. But, it is very dear.
We have to.
What else can we eat?
This rare opportunity for us
get this food.
Captain?
Yes, how?
Not.
Do it now.
Stand. We're sorry.
That pirate ship.
What do you think?
This is really nice.
Very quiet and beautiful.
I want to meet him.
See, there will be plenty of food.
He ​​must be happy.
Hey .. Hey ..
What are you doing? Correct.
- It was the wind.
- You're wrong movement.
It is very difficult.
- Just rotate.
- You know it's hard.
He's just talk.
You're trying to do.
- This is so weird.
- You see the captain came.
He would have been furious.
You do not really work.
Forgive us, captain.
But you know it's hard.
Yes, nice. We can relax alone.
Nothing serious, we can party.
- Partying!
- Yes. That's right.
- You just talk.
- That's right.
You stupid bastards do not know anything.
Do you realize? It is difficult, stupid!
This is just a joke.
You see it there.
Kill it! I'm afraid!
Look at him! That's not possible.
Good. This is great.
He's harmless.
It is not dangerous?
It was very big at all.
I know. He could swallow us directly.
Sure.
But he  benign.
So safe.
- What Really?
- Yes, I really do. He was benign, not usa fear.
Basic coward.
- You, damn! You're damn.
- What?
What scares you?
For what?
You know damn sick!
It's not my fault!
Yes, you see it. It's you!
Get him!
Bitch!
Damn. Cheeky! You're dead!
What the damn?
What is it?
We pirates north.
We will all treasure.
We want it all!
I want you.
- It can not be left off.
- I do not want the old man.
How is this?
We will not be silent.
We are opposed to them.
- How?
- Do not be hasty.
We see the situation.
We need to find a way.
Souma!
If we attack what would you
forgive us and free us?
I will let it, we will see later.
How? Depending on you.
- There's another boat coming.
- Hey!
This is fun. Relaxed.
- Yes, that's right. Let it relax.
- That's right.
True. Ya. Really.
Really good. Ya.
You are absolutely right. It's good.
What is it actually true? You know we
just lazy. Do not want to work.
We're not going to get into trouble if we do not look for it
.
Yes, yes. That's right.
- It was great.
- Yes.
What is this?
Hi, how are you?
Fuck it here!
- Hey, it's you.
- Brother, we could use him.
We better look here.
Yes, great, let's go!
All attack!
- Come on now!
- How?
To get there!
Attack!
Come on! Attack!
Do you miss me?
Yes, this cut.
Hurry!
You help me!
- This is not good, we had to escape.
- Yes.
I pastor.
Do not attack me.
It forgive me.
This is a nice safe.
Why did you all go? Hey
. Why does this go?
You lose! Finally.
He already lost!
Great. Welcome.
Who are you?
I Chang Hyeon.
I'm happy for you.
Chang Hyeon.
Good. We know you're extraordinary.
I'm happy for you, you're great.
Come all, welcome!
Mr. ..
You all will be my slave.
You have to work.
However the two of you must die!
I do not care, as long as you forgive my crew.
- I'm willing to die.
- Yes, it's good for you as captain.
You should give up and be my woman.
It was a great idea.
This is great, we can end peacefully.
This is really good for all.
Not. This is the captain of the ship must die.
You have to die.
Yes, if so.
Can you forgive me.
I can not, I think you should die.
- And what do you want?
- I think I'm better off dead.
This honor dead captain.
I want to die honorably.
This is the only remaining honor.
Oh,
Then I went with him.
For the honor.
- Well.
- Yes.
I have not...
Captain!
Please.
I know you will succeed.
I'm happy to serve my master with this easy problem
.
I'm just asking for a little reward alone,
- Yes, this is a form of loyalty.
- I think it's inappropriate.
- I asked for freedom of the seas.
- This is a big demand.
I think this is hard I gave.
- What else do I ..
- You're just as my legs.
No more than that alone.
Yes, I guess it was not bad.
I'm interested.
- What?
- I want to pay half of the shipping.
Which it from you.
Lord.
Yes? What's this?
We are in the second kubuh.
Why you can not be silent,
We are all prisoners.
Hey. we are not a loser like you.
Do you? Asshole all.
Hey, did you know you lost.
Ah, you're a useless sycophant.
What?
Come! You do, we do not fear.
Did you know we dare!
Really?
Do it!
Gosh ! You think we're scared.
- What do you want to die?
- Come on, attack!
What are you afraid of? You're a coward sea!
- You what?
- Mud sea!
We mud?
- You're a squid.
- Weak!
Yes! Gosh
.
- You what? You are useless silent!
- Choose! You have to choose.
You're all useless.
I do not care!
It is important among us.
Yes! You have to choose!
My God, you're pretentious champion here?
Shut up!
Come opponent.
Can you shut up!
Dead you!
You pretend to sleep.
Not useful.
I have to remove it.
But it was useless. We leave it alone.
We can get married.
It will menghantammu.
You know.
It's all finished. We've eradicate all pirates
.
And make pirate
feet into our hands.
I think this is a good idea is noble.
Yes, yes, no. But it contaminates us.
Yes, that's right.
They Barbarians must we destroy.
Do you understand?
- I think this is good.
- Think what? This decision.
It defame me.
I do not like it.
I want this.
You can see the rest.
All will be safe,
Do not worry about it.
- You will be safe from the warriors.
- I'll see it.
I'll be happy. This is a very important advantage.
Yes.
Why no women here?
This is my gift. This is me.
Young lady to accompany me.
He's good quality.
You're beautiful. You're in luck.
I will be satisfied.
I'm better.
We'll see about that.
It was a beautiful necklace.
It's a gift from my mother .
Prize last.
That?
He was killed.
And raped.
What?
My father was killed.
My mother was raped cruel. I
hidden under the house.
Fuck it very badly!
It was then I became independent.
You're pretty strong.
It's bold, it's no wonder.
My family became victims of the killings.
They brutally killed.
I see it all instantly.
Then you're here for revenge?
I will help-you.
What are your goals?
None. Moreover, we can not
away from each other because of this.
Do not you dare touch me when I'm
sleep.
I'm a real man, I would
do it directly in front of you.
- Of course I'm going to ask for permission.
- Do not be presumptuous.
I'm not attracted to you.
- Do you want to pee?
- Yes.
- You've got a nice body.
- Cover your mouth.
Do not think badly,
I just praise you.
I know a jerk like you.
I've experienced a lot of injuries.
- View my wounds.
- Do not think that only you have.
My wound is very large.
Look, I also have a like-your wound.
- You can see the wound in my back!
- Well I'll show other injuries.
- You're not nothing.
- See there.
You have to be careful around here.
Members  family, father, mother, and child
will be put to death.
Why did this have to happen?
- You're all going to be put to death.
- I failed.
I can not protect you.
You all will be punished tonight.
- Punishment hanging and burned.
- You?
What ?
What's up?
- There's no nothing.
- Not what?
- Shut up.
- Why?
- My butt itches.
- Itching?
- Shut your mouth!
My hands are tied, what can I do?
What I can scratch with my feet?
- Can you help me?
- Forgive him.
- For what you're sorry ?.
- Silence.
For what silence?
- Below. We survived.
- What?
You really want to die quickly.
Warrior! Kill them now!
Come on!
Opened me!
Hey, please open me!
Here!
Hey! Opened for my!
Do not come any closer!
Give up if you do not want to die.
- You've all safe now.
- We owe a lot to you.
It is our duty to help each other.
- No need to hesitate.
- Come on, hurry up.
We're even now.
You're free to go.
- Well, thank you for your cooperation.
- You're a good person.
One day fate will bring us again.
We'll see.
Come...
The most important thing you all survived.
Bad weather.
Appears there will be a storm.
- Better we immediately pulled over.
- Storms will not deter us.
They should fear us.
Well...
not possible. Kill him!
Turn directions!
The entire village was destroyed, there was no food.
- We can not find anything here.
- You've checked everything?
It works kaisarjahat it.
- What do we do?
- Let's attack them.
- Do not do it.
- We live to defend our neighbor.
We just  captive and almost died.
I will go alone.
- I'm with you. Let's go!
- Where are we going?
- He should die!
- Yes!
- We do not kill animals!
- He is an enemy spy.
I am the captain of this ship, you have no right
. Prepare the cannons!
Yes!
- Captain, there!
- What is it?
- Hold attack.
- Everything is ready!
- Prepare your weapon!
Yes!
This time he will die.
Shoot!
Attack!
- Pull! We'll eat well.
- Yes!
Attack!
Hold!
On this ship I just ruling.
You understand?
Yes!
Let him getting closer to death.
- Attack!
- Come on!
Throw a grenade!
- Captain, there is a storm.
- We have to get out of here.
Do not worry, we'll be fine.
- Lift them.
- Lift this whale!
Yes!
Pull with a vengeance!
Come on!
You, this is not your boat!
- You invade me now?
- Because you're too selfish.
I'll tell you one thing.
Yamada, here!
I store explosives in
down there, let us die together.
You decide.
I'm not afraid of your threats. After I killed your
they will be subject to me.
They are all me.
Storm and enemy ships.
Brother.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
Kill them all!
This girl belongs to me, you can attack other
.
- Attack!
Caution!
- Let me through!
- I'm first!
How about one on one?
I came to-mu.
- Take care about yourself.
- What the hell is that.
- Today you're going to die.
- You are going to die.
- Thank you for coming.
- Let's fight together.
Yong-Yi!
I come!
Geez, what's with you?
Gil Dong!
Dead you!
Good job.
There are things you want.
Take it and get out of here.
Quick.
Quick!
Skip, this ship will explode!
- Fast!
- The ship will explode! Skip!
- Hurry!
- Get out of the boat!
Goodbye.
It has become our end.
Successfully!
Do not yell, or
I will kill you.
I just want to talk to you.
Why are you torturing small people?
They were tortured , you squeeze your people
itself. For your well-being.
I'm here to punish your.
I'm here to defend the people.
What have you done?
Forgive us.
Answer me!
You will be put to death.
- We beg pardon, sire.
- Shut up!
- You want to make this country destroyed.
- What?
Close your mouth.
You have no right to speak.
You just deserve to die.
We beg mercy.
We're screwed.
Hey!
- Why are you hanging on a rope?
- I'm working!
Do it right.
Use the force.
- He is very noisy.
- Go to work.
My goodness, I will reply to your later.
- He totally useless.
- He can only use his mouth.
Totally useless.